let savollar15 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "across",
        answer: "B. bo'ylab",
        options: [
            "A. ostida",
            "B. bo'ylab",
            "C. yonida",
            "D. orqali"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to breathe",
        answer: "C. nafas olmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yugurmoq",
            "B. ichmoq",
            "C. nafas olmoq",
            "D. uxlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "characteristic",
        answer: "A. xususiyat",
        options: [
            "A. xususiyat",
            "B. xato",
            "C. xulq-atvor",
            "D. odat"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "to consume",
        answer: "D. iste'mol qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. kuzatmoq",
            "B. tushunmoq",
            "C. tushuntirmoq",
            "D. iste'mol qilmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "to excite",
        answer: "B. hayajonlantirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. zeriktirmoq",
            "B. hayajonlantirmoq",
            "C. qo'rqitmoq",
            "D. tinchlantirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "extreme",
        answer: "A. haddan tashqari",
        options: [
            "A. haddan tashqari",
            "B. normal",
            "C. o'rtacha",
            "D. kam"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "fear",
        answer: "D. qo'rquv",
        options: [
            "A. jasorat",
            "B. quvonch",
            "C. sevgi",
            "D. qo'rquv"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "fortunate",
        answer: "B. omadli",
        options: [
            "A. qayg'uli",
            "B. omadli",
            "C. baxtsiz",
            "D. umidsiz"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "to happen to",
        answer: "A. tasodifan sodir bo'lmoq",
        options: [
            "A. tasodifan sodir bo'lmoq",
            "B. oldini olmoq",
            "C. rejalashtirmoq",
            "D. nazorat qilmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "length",
        answer: "C. uzunlik",
        options: [
            "A. kenglik",
            "B. balandlik",
            "C. uzunlik",
            "D. chuqurlik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "mistake",
        answer: "B. xato",
        options: [
            "A. muvaffaqiyat",
            "B. xato",
            "C. yechim",
            "D. imkoniyat"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "to observe",
        answer: "A. kuzatmoq",
        options: [
            "A. kuzatmoq",
            "B. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "C. uxlamoq",
            "D. o'ylamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "opportunity",
        answer: "D. imkoniyat",
        options: [
            "A. qiyinchilik",
            "B. muammo",
            "C. xavf",
            "D. imkoniyat"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "prize",
        answer: "C. mukofot",
        options: [
            "A. yo'qotish",
            "B. jazo",
            "C. mukofot",
            "D. vazifa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "race",
        answer: "B. poyga",
        options: [
            "A. sayr",
            "B. poyga",
            "C. tanaffus",
            "D. o'yin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "to realize",
        answer: "A. anglamoq",
        options: [
            "A. anglamoq",
            "B. be'parvo qoldirmoq",
            "C. oldini olmoq",
            "D. unutmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to respond",
        answer: "B. javob bermoq",
        options: [
            "A. jim turmoq",
            "B. javob bermoq",
            "C. unutmoq",
            "D. o'ylamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "risk",
        answer: "A. xavfli tavakkal",
        options: [
            "A. xavfli tavakkal",
            "B. xavfsizlik",
            "C. muvaffaqiyat",
            "D. foyda"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "to wonder",
        answer: "C. hayron bo'lmoq",
        options: [
            "A. bilmoq",
            "B. oldini olmoq",
            "C. hayron bo'lmoq",
            "D. tushuntirmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "yet",
        answer: "B. hali",
        options: [
            "A. allaqachon",
            "B. hali",
            "C. keyinroq",
            "D. darhol"
        ]
    }
];
